{
    "subject": "Rajan_Khosa",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Dance_of_the_Wind",
    "human_readable": "Rajan Khosa created Dance of the Wind.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9413151144981384,
            "question": "Has Rajan Khosa created any other dances besides 'Dance of the Wind'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8992835879325867,
            "question": "What is the significance of 'Dance of the Wind' in Rajan Khosa's career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8605563044548035,
            "question": "What is the name of the dance created by Rajan Khosa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8061222434043884,
            "question": "Who created the dance called 'Dance of the Wind'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.619574785232544,
            "question": "What type of art did Rajan Khosa create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44011926651000977,
            "question": "Where has 'Dance of the Wind' been performed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4116296172142029,
            "question": "Is 'Dance of the Wind' a well-known performance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4082289934158325,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the inspiration behind 'Dance of the Wind'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3753049075603485,
            "question": "Who are some other famous choreographers like Rajan Khosa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3520438075065613,
            "question": "What are some characteristics of 'Dance of the Wind'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Rajan Khosa created Dance of the Wind.",
            "html": "yago_15558_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some other famous choreographers like Rajan Khosa?",
            "html": "yago_15558_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the inspiration behind 'Dance of the Wind'?",
            "html": "yago_15558_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'Dance of the Wind' a well-known performance?",
            "html": "yago_15558_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_15558_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_15558_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_15558_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_15558_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_15558_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_15558_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_15558_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_15558_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_15558_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_15558_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the structured JSON format for your query:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis indicates that the statement \"Rajan Khosa created Dance of the Wind\" is supported by the documents. The document with file path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_15558/re-ranker-msmarco/25.txt, for example, explicitly mentions Rajan Khosa's debut feature film as \"Dance of the Wind\", which was set in the world of Indian classical music and dealt with teacher/disciple relationship."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Rajan Khosa created Dance of the Wind.\" Specifically, multiple documents mention Rajan Khosa as the director of the film Dance of the Wind (1997), indicating he was involved in its creation."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}